

Prem Naseer A

Test Automation Engineer

CONTACT ME

Contact No: +919342071159 Email: npanaseer@gmail.com Address: 3/133, F1-6, Kaveri St, Medvakkam Chennai, TN

EDUCATION

MBA Finance

Loyola University, Chennai, 2018

BE, ECE

Anna University Chennai, 2015

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Selenium WebDriver

TestNG

Maven

Cucumber

Eclipse IDE

JIRA

SKILLS

Project Management
Time Management
Problem Solving
Team Work
Adaptability

COMPETENCE

Automation Testing
Regression Testing
Smoke & Sanity Testing
Agile Methodology

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Overall, 7 years of experience which 1.6 years in Software Quality Assurance Testing of Web, CRM application and Travel web Applications. Experience in all stages of the Software Development Life Cycle and QA Life Cycle. 5.6 year's experience as Senior Technical Support Engineer. Experienced in installing and repairing software and applications, troubleshooting, and conducting regular tests and maintenance to ensure smooth workflow.

ROLES & RESPONSEBILITIES

- Analyzing the requirements and reviewing the test case document.
- Executing the test cases and identifying defects.
- Reporting the testing status in daily scrum meetings.
- Performing Smoke testing, UAT testing, and Regression testing.
- Performing test closure activities.
- Following up with developers on defects status daily.
- Responsible for test delivery of cases & results.
- Creating automated functional regression test scripts using Selenium WebDriver. Executing the automated regression test cases during every release.
- Enhance the existing automation scripts during functionality enhancement.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Test Engineer

NilaaPay Big Source Private Limited | Chennai | Mar 2021 - present

Project: NilaaPay Web Application (E-commerce Portal)

Description: To design and develop software that would automate the major product operations through NillaaPay E-commerce Webpage which serves a multiple offer to NilaaPay user. The Major module is Member portal, Product available status, and Order Summery.

Subject Matter Expert

Sutherland Global Service | Chennai | April 2019 - Mar 2021

Project: MS Web Applications

Description:

Creating Bug for Emerging & challenging issues which affect end user experience. Advanced troubleshooting in attaining resolution whichever was not resolved at Level 1 Technical support. Root Cause Analysis (DSAT analysis) in identifying defects and coaching agents on the same

Technical Support Engineer

Sutherland Global Service | Chennai | Oct 2015 - Mar 2019

Project: MS Windows

Description: Optimized customer experience by delivering superior services and effectively troubleshooting issues. Creating Bug for Emerging & challenging issues that affect customer experience. Handling OneDrive, Office 365, Edge, and Microsoft store app issues.